<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Surfers page</title><link>http://localhost/Goga_projekt_pHp/index.php</link><description>News from surfers points round the Globe</description><item><title> The World Surf League (WSL) released the full schedule for the 2019 Championship Tour (CT)</title><link>http://localhost/Goga_projekt_pHp/commands.php?command=2&amp;new_id=5</link><description>Surfing is truly a global pursuit, and for those looking to live the endless summer, here is the calendar of 2019 surf events that will ensure that you always have sand between your toes.</description><pubDate>2019-01-19 11:21:43</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Things to now when you start surfing</title><link>http://localhost/Goga_projekt_pHp/commands.php?command=2&amp;new_id=2</link><description>From our experience, surfing becomes more fun the more you progress. We know there is a path to accelerate the process of learning to surf and we want to share it with you. Here are the top 5 things we think a beginner/intermediate surfer should know when</description><pubDate>2019-01-18 22:53:13</pubDate></item><item><title>The surfing boards list</title><link>http://localhost/Goga_projekt_pHp/commands.php?command=2&amp;new_id=4</link><description>Surfing is not a complicated sport. Unlike many other water sports, the truth is that surfing only requires a surfboard and someone willing to glide over the ocean waves.</description><pubDate>2019-01-18 22:46:54</pubDate></item><item><title>Top 5 Best Beaches for Beginners to Learn To Surf in Bali</title><link>http://localhost/Goga_projekt_pHp/commands.php?command=2&amp;new_id=3</link><description>Bali is often considered one of the ultimate playgrounds for surfers. While the island is mostly famous because of its expert surf spots, Bali also has surf spots for beginners where novice surfers can safely learn surf basics.</description><pubDate>2019-01-18 22:42:52</pubDate></item><item><title>Shark Attack</title><link>http://localhost/Goga_projekt_pHp/commands.php?command=2&amp;new_id=1</link><description>Why do sharks attack? Sharks are carnivorous and may be found in all seas. Sometimes, they associate humans with food.</description><pubDate>2019-01-18 22:39:35</pubDate></item></channel></rss>